xerpi.com 2007-06-09

# Xerpi, love your favorites

GoDo Media LLC ("GoDo") has adopted the following general policy toward copyright infringement in accordance with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act. The address of GoDo's Designated Agent to Receive Notification of Claimed Infringement ("Designated Agent") is listed at the end of this policy.  
It is GoDo's policy to (1) block access to or remove material that it believes in good faith to be copyrighted material that has been illegally copied and distributed by any of our users; and (2) remove and discontinue service to repeat offenders.

## A. Procedure for Reporting Copyright Infringements:

If you believe that material or content residing on the GoDo website infringes a copyright, please send a notice of copyright infringement containing the following information, in English, to the Designated Agent listed below:

  1. A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright that has been allegedly infringed;
  2. Identification of works or materials being infringed;
  3. Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing including information regarding the location of the infringing materials that the copyright owner seeks to have removed, with sufficient detail so that GoDo is capable of finding and verifying its existence;
  4. Contact information about the notifier including address, telephone number and, if available, e-mail address;
  5. A statement that the notifier has a good faith belief that the material is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and 
  6. A statement made under penalty of perjury that the information provided is accurate and the notifying party is authorized to make the complaint on behalf of the copyright owner. 

## B. Once Proper Bona Fide Infringement Notification is Received by the Designated Agent:

It is GoDo's policy:

  1. to remove or disable access to the infringing material; 
  2. to notify the user that it has removed or disabled access to the material; and 
  3. that repeat offenders will have the infringing material removed from the system and that GoDo will terminate such user's access to the website and service.

## C. Procedure to Supply a Counter-Notice to the Designated Agent:

If the user believes that the material that was removed or to which access was disabled is either not infringing, or the user believes that it has the right to post and use such material from the copyright owner, the copyright owner's agent, or pursuant to the law, the user must send a counter-notice containing the following information, in English, to the Designated Agent listed below:

  1. A physical or electronic signature of the user;
  2. Identification of the material that has been removed or to which access has been disabled and the location at which the material appeared before it was removed or disabled;
  3. A statement that the user has a good faith belief that the material was removed or disabled as a result of mistake or a misidentification of the material; and
  4. User's name, address, telephone number, and, if available, e-mail address and a statement that such person or entity consents to the jurisdiction of the Federal Court for the judicial district in which the user's address is located, or if the user's address is located outside the United States, for any judicial district in which GoDo is located, and that such person or entity will accept service of process from the person who provided notification of the alleged infringement.

If a counter-notice is received by the Designated Agent, GoDo may send a copy of the counter-notice to the original complaining party informing that person that it may replace the removed material or cease disabling it in 10 business days. Unless the copyright owner files an action seeking a court order against the user, the removed material may be replaced or access to it restored in 10 to 14 business days after receipt of the counter-notice, at GoDo's discretion.  
The GoDo Copyright Administrator for notice of claims of copyright or other intellectual property infringement can be reached as follows:

Copyrightnotice@godo.co.uk

Please note that, due to security concerns, attachments cannot be accepted. Accordingly, any notification of infringement submitted electronically with an attachment will not be received or processed.

GoDo Media LLC ("GoDo") and its affiliated Web sites respect your privacy. This Privacy Statement applies to information collection and usage on the GoDo Web sites.

## Collection of Personal Information

You may visit GoDo Web sites without submitting any personally identifiable information about yourself. We do collect clickstream data about all users of the GoDo Web sites, including behavioral data, IP addresses, log files and traffic data.  
The submission of personal information (such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address, telephone number, social security number and financial information) may be required in order to obtain certain products or services available on the GoDo Web sites.  
We may also collect demographic information such as your postal code, age, gender, interests and preferences. Submission of any such information may be in the form of surveys, contest entries or other information requests and is voluntary.  
We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:  
Information we receive from you through our Web sites, including forms and applications completed by you; Information about your transactions with us and the companies that work with us to provide products and services to you; Information about you that we may receive from credit reporting agencies or other third parties.

## Use and Disclosure of Personal Information

Information collected from or about you through the GoDo Web sites may be combined with other information collected or acquired by us.  
We may disclose all of the information we collect from or about you to third parties to provide the products and services requested by you. You consent to such disclosures by completing the form or application used for requesting such products or services on the GoDo Web sites. You understand and agree that such third parties may use, analyze and further disclose the information in order to provide you with the products and services you have requested.  
We may use all of the information we collect from or about you for purposes of analyzing user behavior, improving our Web sites, improving our products and services, researching our users needs and otherwise for development of our Web sites. In some cases, we may contract with third parties to perform these activities for us and may disclose personally identifiable information about you to such third party vendors. Such third party vendors will be required to maintain the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information and will be prohibited from using the information for any other purpose.  
Other than as set forth above or as required or permitted under applicable law, we will not disclose personally identifiable information about you to any non-affiliated third parties.  
We may use the information collected from and about you to periodically send you promotional or information messages. You agree that we may send you information messages about products or services requested by you and any activities related thereto. With respect to other promotional and information messages, you will be given the option of opting out of further receipt of such messages each time a message is sent. We may use and disclose non-personally identifiable information, whether in the aggregate or otherwise, for any purpose.

## Cookies

GoDo Web sites use cookies to recognize you when you visit the sites, to personalize your experience and to enhance your experience at the sites. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer's hard drive by our computers that help us identify your computer and track traffic patterns. If you don't want to receive cookies, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser Please be aware, however, that if you disable cookies there may be portions of or features of the GoDo Web sites that will not operate properly. Information obtained from or about you may be stored in a cookie on your hard drive and may be used, among other things, to pre-fill forms and applications on the GoDo Web sites.

## Storage and Security of Personal Information

GoDo uses a variety of security technologies and procedures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access. We restrict access to non-public personal information about you only to those that need to know the information in order to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and other procedural safeguards to comply with applicable privacy laws to protect your non-public personal information. However, if your information is forwarded to a third party provider, your information will be transmitted according to security and privacy policies and practices of such third party provider.

## Web Beacons

GoDo may use Web beacons (also referred to as pixel tags or single-pixel gifs) to measure site usage and behavior.

## Changes to the Privacy Statement

We may periodically update this Privacy Statement to reflect customer feedback and current practices by updating this Privacy Statement on our Web sites. Please be sure to check back frequently.  
GoDo would like to hear from you regarding this Privacy Statement If you have feedback or believe that we have violated this Privacy Statement, please email us at contact@xerpi.com.
